Can a small group of drones guarantee the safety and reliability of railways and, at the same time, help railway operators save billions of euros each year?
一小群无人机能否保障铁路的安全性和可靠性，同时帮助铁路运营商每年节省数十亿欧元？
That is the very likely future of applying today’s “eyes in the sky” technology to making sure that the millions of kilometres of rail tracks and infrastructure worldwide are safe for trains on a 24/7 basis.
这极有可能就是当今“空中之眼”技术未来的应用前景：用它来确保全球数百万公里的铁轨和基础设施全天候都能让列车安全通行。
Drones are already being used to examine high-tension electrical lines.
无人机目前已被用于检查高压输电线。
They could do precisely the same thing to inspect railway lines and other vital aspects of rail infrastructure such as the correct position of railway tracks and switching points.
它们可以用完全相同的方式检查铁路线路以及铁路基础设施的其他重要方面，比如铁轨和道岔的位置是否正确。
The more regularly the lines can be inspected, the more railway safety, reliability and on-time performance will be improved.
线路检查得越频繁，铁路的安全性、可靠性和准点率就提高得越多。
Costs would be cut and operations would be more efficient across the board.
成本会降低，运营也会全面变得更加高效。
That includes huge savings in maintenance costs and better protection of railway personnel.
这包括大幅节省维护成本，以及更好地保护铁路工作人员。
It is calculated that European railways alone spend approximately 20 billion euros a year on maintenance, including sending maintenance staff, often at night, to inspect and repair the rail infrastructure.
据计算，仅欧洲的铁路每年就在维护上花费约200亿欧元，其中包括派遣维护人员去检查和维修铁路基础设施，而且常常是在夜间。
That can be dangerous work that could be avoided with drones assisting the crews’ efforts.
这类工作可能有危险，而如果有无人机协助工作人员作业，这类工作就可以避免。
By using the latest technologies, drones could also start providing higher-value services for railways, detecting faults in the rail or switches, before they can cause any safety problems.
借助最新技术，无人机还可以开始为铁路提供更高价值的服务，在铁轨或道岔的故障引发任何安全问题之前就把它们检测出来。
To perform these tasks, drones for rail don’t need to be flying overhead.
要完成这些任务，铁路无人机并不需要在空中飞行。
Engineers are now working on a new concept: the rail drones of the future.
工程师们目前正在研究一个新概念：未来的铁路无人机。
They will be moving on the track ahead of the train, and programmed to run autonomously.
它们将在列车前方的轨道上行驶，并通过编程实现自主运行。
Very small drones with advanced sensors and AI, travelling ahead of the train, could guide it like a co-pilot.
配备先进传感器和人工智能的微型无人机在列车前方行进，可以像副驾驶一样为列车引路。
With their ability to see ahead, they could signal any problem, so that fast-moving trains would be able to react in time.
凭借察看前方的能力，它们一旦发现任何问题都能发出信号，让高速行驶的列车能够及时作出反应。